in your word.
>> Will you wash me?
>> Holy.
>> Will you please
me?
>> Lord, make me holy. Holy.
>> Will you watch me?
>> White snow.
>> Sometimes, Lord, this life is rough.
At times we feel we've had enough.
But with all the sin in the world today,
we need you, Lord, to wash us clean.
Will you?
>> Uh, happy Sabbath, brothers and sisters.
We going to start with the reading of
the law like we do every Sabbath
in every location that we are located in
throughout the earth. We going to start
reading at Exodus 20
verses 1-17.
Exodus 20:es 1-1 17.
When you get it, go ahead and read, my
brother. And God spake all these words,
saying, I am the Lord thy God, which
hath brought thee out of the land of
Egypt, out of the house of bondage. Thou
shalt have no other gods before me. Thou
shalt not make unto thee any grave in
image, or any likeness of anything that
is in heaven above, or that is in the
earth beneath, or that is in the water
under the earth. Thou shalt not bow thou
thyself to them, nor serve them. For I,
the Lord thy God, am a jealous God,
visiting the iniquity of the fathers
upon the children, to the third and
fourth generation, of them that hate me,
and showing mercy unto thousands of them
that love me, and keep my commandments.
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain. For the Lord will not
hold him guiltless that taketh his name
in vain. Remember the Sabbath day to
keep it holy. Six days shalt thou labor
and do all thy work. But the seventh day
is the Sabbath of the Lord thy God. In
it thou shalt not do any work. Thou nor
thy son, nor thy daughter, thy man's
servant, nor thy maid servant, nor thy
cattle, nor thy stranger that is within
thy gates. For in six days the Lord made
heaven and earth, the sea, and all that
in them is, and rested the seventh day.
Wherefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath
day, and hallowed it. Honor thy father
and thy mother uh that thy days may be
long upon the land which the Lord thy
God giveth thee. Thou shalt not kill.
Thou shalt not commit adultery. Thou
shalt not steal. Thou shalt not bear
false witnesses against thy neighbor.
Thou shalt not coveret thy neighbor's
house. Thou shalt not coveret thy
neighbor's wife, nor his man's servant,
nor his maid's servant, nor his ox, nor
his ass, nor anything that is thy
neighbors.
>> Those are the 10 commandments spoken by
the Lord personally himself to our
forefathers coming down on Mount Si when
we came out of Egypt in the wilderness.
Praise God for that to give us that
directly. Right, Spanky?
>> Correct. Let's go to uh Ecclesiastes 12
and get it from the wisest man with the
exception of Jesus Christ that walked
the earth even the richest king Solomon.
Ecclesiastes 12 13 and 14 to get the
conclusion of the whole matter. Go
ahead.
>> Let us hear the conclusion of the whole
matter. Fear God and keep his
commandments. For this is the whole duty
of man. For God shall bring every work
into judgment with every secret thing
whether it be good or whether it be
evil. Yes, sir. Now, let's go to
Revelation 22
and read verses 14 and 15.
and we going to read verses 14 and 15.
When you get it, go ahead and read.
>> Blessed are they that do his
commandments, that they may have right
to the tree of life, and may enter
through the gates into the city. For
without are dogs and sorcerers, and
whoreongers, and murderers, and
idolattors, whosoever loveth and maketh
a lie.
>> There you have it, sisters and brothers.
Jesus Christ the same yesterday, today,
and forever. Therefore, we have it in
Revelation, Ecclesiastes,
and in the past with Moses in Genesis,
all the way down to Exodus, all the way
down through the prophets, all the way
down through Matthew the John the
Revelator to keep these commandments.
all over the book became mistaken.
But however, happy Sabbath, brothers and
sisters.
>> Happy Sabbath.
>> It is a pleasure to stand before you on
the Lord Sabbath day. All glory to him
in the mighty name of Jesus Christ
because that's why we are here today.
Like he told us when we came out of
Egypt in Exodus 19, I bear you on
eagle's wings and I brought you unto
myself.
You ain't come here just because off
your own intuition. God had to give you
the instructions to keep his Sabbath day
holy and have a holy convocation. So, he
brought you here.
>> Right.
>> I like to say, "Welcome home." If y'all
new, anybody new, you know, get
comfortable. We preach the word by
subject and title so you could get a
thorough understanding of what we deal
dealing with so you won't be oblivious
to what we teaching.
So, my name is Brother Alvin for those
who don't know me and uh reading for us
today. Brother uh Cardin, brother Spanky
to me. You know, I call him Brother
Spanky. But uh we going to preach this
word. We going to enjoy ourselves holy
convocation that the Lord commanded us
and preferably he would smile down upon
us for taking heed to his word and
trying to keep his commandment. Amen.
>> Amen.
>> Praise the Lord. So the subject and the
title that we going to deal with today
is for thine is the kingdom
and the power
and the glory forever. Amen.
>> Amen.
>> Once again
for it is the Lord kingdom. It is the
Lord's power and it is his glory
forever. Because he don't die. He don't
have no beginning of days nor end of
life. So he will obtain and possess this
thing forever. Amen. So this is where
he's going to give us opportunity to
take hold of so it can we can have the
kingdom.
We can have the power and we can have
the glory forever. Amen.
>> Amen. Amen.
>> And it is imperative, brothers and
sisters, that we listen to God to learn
how to operate with the capacity of
knowledge, wisdom, and understanding
that he provides us, seeing that the
kingdom and the power and the glory
belongs unto him even forever.
So that we could take part of the same
even the divine nature. Right? All
things are of God
who have reconciled us to himself by
Jesus Christ and have given us the
ministry of reconciliation so we could
go out and recover the world so they
could take part of the kingdom, the
power and the glory forever. You see
what I'm saying?
>> Yes, sir. to recover ourself as well and
those who will be saved due to the fall
of men that took place in the garden of
Eden.
So, we are in recovery, people. Like I
say, this is a clinic. This is a
hospital. This is my seventh day
appointment that I uh make every Sabbath
day.
And I'm here to get my prescription
filled. And it is none other than the
word of God,
>> right?
>> That is in that prescription, right?
because he said, "I sent my word and it
healed them." So, this is the thing
that's going to heal heal us. It's going
to purify us. It's going to make us
clean. It's going to show us how to
operate, people.
And for the most part,
God has given us proper guidance
that we need. However, take note of
this. Don't waste your time with people
that refuse to be about your father's
business.
Jesus tell tells us that in the
scriptures.
Don't waste your time on people that
don't want to hear this thing. Keep it
moving like Deshawn always say when we
go out on the outreach with the family.
Don't be trying to teach them a whole
lesson. You just trying to get them here
to class so they can get understanding
and information so they can get out
there with us and help us cuz we need
help. Right, brother?
>> Right.
>> So, let's look at this subject and this
title again. I'mma rehearse it again.
For thine is the kingdom and the power
and the glory forever. And we want to
take part of the same. So who we need to
model ourself after. Let's go to Hebrews
3 and1. I ain't going to have you here
that long. I'm going to get you in and
out like in and out burger.
>> Right. Spanky,
>> right?
>> Animal style.
>> To start putting me up on that in Vegas,
boy.
Well, I'mma leave that alone.
Hebrews 3 and 1. Let's consider uh our
high priest.
>> Hebrews 3 and 1. When the church get
there, say amen.
>> Go ahead and read. Spanky.
>> Wherefore, holy brethren, partakers of
the heavenly calling, consider the
apostle and high priest of our
profession, Christ Jesus. Consider him
what he taught us, even how he walked
and how he will have us to walk. Showing
us the instructions of everlasting life.
That's what Jesus did when he came into
the earth. Showing us how to please the
father.
>> Because this thing came from heaven,
people.
Ain't that beautiful?
>> You didn't get this from offline, from
off Tik Tok. You didn't get it off
Facebook. You ain't get it OUT YOUR
HOROSCOPE. THIS HERE come from heaven,
Jack. And we had to have a specific
messenger to convey that message from
the father to us. And I don't think none
of us got the zip code to where they
come from.
>> Right.
>> Right. This thing come from heaven. John
6 and 38. We going to validate it. Ain't
we spank because we like to prove our
point. Right.
>> Right. Right. Right. And Sean, if we get
in this book and we read this book TO
PROVE THUS SAYETH the Lord, not what's
on our mind
>> facts
>> because our thoughts and our opinion is
strictly prohibited.
>> Let's show you this thing came from
heaven.
Even the messenger of the covenant, even
Jesus Christ, the anointed one, high
priest, king of kings, lord of lord, the
lamb of God who take away the sins of
the world. John 6 and 38. Go ahead and
read spank. For I came down from heaven,
not to do my own will.
>> He came from Lavine.
>> No, heaven.
>> Aenddale,
>> heaven.
>> Tempe,
>> CHADLER,
>> HEAVEN.
>> SANTAN VALLEY,
>> OUGHT TO BE WELL,
>> HEAVEN.
>> Priny Green,
>> heaven.
>> He come from heaven. Jackow.
>> Which one of y'all been there?
>> Nobody.
So, I think we got some vital
information
here. Go ahead and read, my brother.
>> But the will of him that sent me,
>> not to do my own will, but the will of
him that sent me. Jesus came to the
earth for one purpose, people,
and that is to do the will of the
father.
>> Amen.
Therefore, he will speak
not his own words, but what he was
commanded to speak. And let's validate
that. I don't want you to take my word
for it. I want to show you in the
scriptures, even the testimony. John 12
and 49.
Jesus came from heaven
in the land uninhabited by man.
And man would never go there. and he
came to give us that which the father
have given him
and he walked in the same order.
So he's not hypocritical
or he's not going to give you something
that he didn't have to do.
>> Right?
>> You see what I'm saying? So let's see
what the Lord has given us.
John 12 and 49. Go ahead and read, my
brother.
>> For I have not spoken of myself.
>> What'd he say?
>> He's not speaking OF HIS OWN WORDS.
GUARD and breathe.
>> But the father which sent me.
>> Mhm.
>> He gave me a commandment.
>> He did what?
>> And what else?
>> What I should say
>> and what else?
>> And what I should speak.
>> So who gave Jesus the word people?
>> The father.
>> Man, the invisible GOD. AIN'T NONE OF US
EVER SEEN.
But he gave us a message so we can
reconcile oursel and recover ourself
so that we may take part in the kingdom.
and in the divine power and in the glory
even forever my sisters and brothers
for it is pertaining to the kingdom of
the father
all this information that Jesus has
brought us to give unto us and the
father's power and his glories
concerning how we can take part in the
same even forever John 6 and 47 7 John 6
and 47. But you got to believe in this
word cuz it's impossible to please God
without faith. Right.
>> That's right.
>> For those that come to God must believe
that he is and that he is a rewarder of
those that diligently seek him. I mean,
don't be slothful. Don't just read on
the Sabbath. You got to diligently seek
him.
You know what I mean?
Me and Sister Gwen have time when we
read on Tuesday. I've been slothful and
I thought about it like, man, I need to
get to work.
But we do these things to keep our mind
focused on what the prize is,
>> right?
>> You see what I'm saying?
>> Yeah.
>> And I have to tell that sister, I'm
sleepy now. That sister read, you hear
me?
>> Ain't no stopping. Like you want to keep
going. It ain't no stopping.
And that's what we need.
>> You know, cuz anything you rehearse
yourself in and practice all the time,
you can only get better.
>> That's right.
>> Right.
>> And it's the word that's going to heal
us, people. John 6 and 47. You got to
believe this thing. Go ahead and read.
What did Jesus say?
>> Verily, verily I say unto you,
>> TRULY, TRULY, THAT'S WHAT THAT MEAN. I
SAY UNTO YOU, what he say, Spank,
>> he that believeth on me hath everlasting
life. If you believe that word that the
father gave him that he give to you,
what it's going to get you people?
>> Everlasting life.
Come on. You want the 12 months of
scripture for Netflix. I want
everlasting life.
So it is according to your faith and
your belief sisters cuz he said and
brothers because he said whosoever
believe on me have everlasting life
even in the words of the father that he
has brought unto us. There's no other
way people. There's no other way to
salvation. And ain't it's a ain't it a
blessing for us to be able to have the
information that's going to get the
world salvation? Yeah,
>> you could tell it to your coworker, to
the cashier at Walmart.
>> We can help these people get salvation.
We don't know what is in our lap today
and what we understand.
>> Cuz by the words of God, the heavens
were created, even me and you.
He created man from the dust of the
ground and breathed into his nostril the
breath of life and man became a living
soul. Right.
>> Right.
>> He spoke IT THOUGH. RIGHT. LET US CREATE
MAN IN our image after our own likeness.
>> So if we continue to walk in this word
people, we gonna make the transformation
from this flesh and blood body that
hurt, pinch you hard enough, you going
to be like, what you doing
to a body that if I did that, it
wouldn't even penetrate you.
You see what I'm saying?
>> Yeah. So
we want to receive the kingdom, the
power and the glory forever people by
Jesus Christ.
So we could possess this kingdom. So we
could possess this power and this glory
forever. Not temporarily, forever. Cuz
when Jesus came out of the grave in
Matthew 28 and 18, WHAT HE SAY? ALL
POWER IS GIVEN to me in heaven and
earth.
And that's what he want to give us
through his instructions that is given
us within the word of God. You know why?
63.
>> It is the spirit that quickenth.
>> That's what's going to make you alive.
Go ahead. Spank.
>> The flesh profitth nothing.
>> Your flesh ain't going to do nothing BUT
STANK AND ROT AND DEC uh decompose.
>> But what that word going to do, Spanky?
The words that I speak unto you, they
are spirit and they are life.
>> To instruct you people
to instruct you to get this prized
possession.
Let's go to first Thessalonian the 2
chapter
to instruct you brothers and sisters.
That word is what's going to quicken us.
Quicken mean to make alive.
Don't y'all want to live forever?
>> Yeah.
>> We done seen death since Adam
>> throughout this creation.
>> Every state, city, country we go to,
they got graveyards.
>> Do because we lost the information and
access to the tree OF LIFE TO TELL US
how to stop dying. All right.
However, people these instructions is
given to us so we know how to obtain
salvation. 1 Thessalonians 2 and 12. Go
ahead and read.
>> That you will walk worthy of God.
>> So you can walk worthy of God. Go ahead
and read.
>> Who haveath called you unto his kingdom
and glory
>> and power forever. Then he say he called
you to his kingdom. Read it again.
Spanky believers
>> that that ye would walk worthy of God
who who hath called you unto his kingdom
and glory.
>> He called you unto his kingdom
and his glory
and his power even forever. M
>> John 3 and5 show you what Jesus said how
you can get into this kingdom cuz we
need to know how to obtain this kingdom
this power this glory forever right
>> we need to know how to reach this
potential right
>> so let's see
let's take a look at
John the 3 chapter and we going to pick
it up at verse Vers 5 and see what the
master say. Y'all believe Jesus, right?
>> Yes, we do.
>> You ain't got to believe me. I don't
want you to believe me. Believe what's
in this book. Let's see what Jesus said.
Read.
>> Jesus answered, "Verily, verily, I say
unto thee, except a man be born of water
and of the spirit, he cannot enter into
the kingdom of God."
>> So this how you get into this kingdom.
This how you obtain this glory, this
power forever.
If you be born of the water and that's
the word of God
and you got to be born of the spirit.
You have to make a physical change.
>> You cannot enter into the kingdom of God
flesh and blood or have a carnal mind.
You can, but you going in the lake of
fire.
You won't be on the good side of the
kingdom. So in order for you to make
this process and get into this kingdom,
you have to
be purified by this word and you have to
make a physical change. Indeed, that
mean to be born again. This is how
the word
is going to get you into this kingdom.
Let's go to Revelation 22 and 14. This
is the only way
by the word of truth
and keeping God's commandment.
And I'mma prove it. I'm going to prove
it.
You come up out of this jacket.
Feeling like Steve Harvey in this boy.
Somebody said
confidence. I mean, my son got down on
me today when I came in talking about
preacher Paul. Oh, that's Oh, that's
what we on, huh?
Wait till I barbecue barbecue for you
next time. That going to be salty.
>> No. Praise the Lord. I love you, son.
Let's show you how we get into this
kingdom. You have to be born of the
spirit.
Meaning, you got to have a physical
change
and
you have to uh
be born of the water. This word of God,
Revelation 22 and 14, go ahead and read.
>> Blessed are they that do his
commandments.
>> You become blessed. Go ahead and read.
that they may have right to the tree of
life.
>> You get access back to Jesus. Go ahead
and read.
>> And may enter and through the gates into
the city.
>> And you may enter through the gates into
the city. That's a bargain you can't
beat, can you?
>> Nope.
>> Three for one.
>> HE SAID YOU BECOME BLESSED.
>> YEAH.
>> RIGHT.
>> YEP.
>> And you get access TO THE TREE OF LIFE,
JESUS. This all in the brochure, y'all.
It's called a Barbie.
>> And you may enter into the gates into
the city.
>> And you thought Disney World was summer.
>> Wait till you see this kingdom with
streets of gold like transparent glass.
That mean you could look through the
streets.
>> Man, ain't that a blessing?
>> Yeah.
So,
how do we take part in the blessings of
this great city? Let's go to Isaiah 19.
Let's show you how we take part in the
blessings of this great city.
>> Hey, uh, you want to do that?
>> In any other city, any other city for
that matter.
>> You want to do Revelations 21 and 10?
>> Excuse me.
>> Revelation 21 and 10.
Yeah, let's do that. Let's do that.
Let's look at the city. Oh, okay. Let's
Thanks, Spanky. Well, it's good to have
your reader. He be on He be on his toes.
He be on his toes. So, like I said, for
this one word,
that's what universe mean. One word. You
only mean one verse mean word. So for
all you all the universe, one word will
get you three
>> overwhelming prizes.
>> Get you blessed, get you access to the
tree of life and get you access inside
of the city right
>> through the gates.
>> Let's show you what city we talking
about.
In my notes, I got what city?
>> Revelation 21 and 10. Go ahead and read.
And he carried me away in the spirit to
a great and high mountain.
>> And what did he show?
>> And showed me the great city.
>> What was that?
>> The holy Jerusalem.
>> This is the city we talking about. Where
is coming from?
>> Descending out of heaven from God.
>> Man,
that's not no co coincidence that the
word came from heaven,
>> right?
>> The city going to come from heaven.
That's why it's called the kingdom of
heaven.
>> Even in the Lord's prayer, it say which
art in heaven, thy kingdom what?
>> Come. Thy will be done in earth as it is
in heaven.
>> We just validated that. Right. Right.
>> Let's go to Revelation, I mean Isaiah uh
1 and9 so we can uh
know what we need to do to take part in
the blessings of this great city.
Let's check that out. And any other
city, like I said,
uhoh.
Out of the mouth of babes, he ordained
strength
to steal the avenger and the enemy.
Isaiah 1 and 19. How we going to obtain
this blessing, brother, to take part
in this city? Go ahead and read.
>> If you be willing and obedient,
>> you got to be obedient.
Then what?
>> Ye shall eat the good of the land.
>> Then you gonna eat the good of the land.
>> You feel me? Y'all sisters doing a lot
of laughing over there now. Like it's
the preacher time now.
>> Come on now. We don't want to distract
the congre.
>> All right. I got the mic. Like brother
Stevie saying
Fort Lauderdale. I got the mic. Y'all
y'all get the mic later on. All right.
when we do the Q&A.
No disrespect, sisters and brothers,
though, but we have to maintain order.
They having too much fun. Like, what
they talking about?
So, if you be willing and obedient,
excuse me, you can eat the good of the
land. Deuteronomy 30 and 10.
Deuteronomy 30 and 10. Them sisters
going to stone me, boy.
For real. What was you on up there? Cuz
you had your little vest on like
right down like no it ain't even like
that. For sure fellas
like no that's on you.
Deuteronomy 30 and10. If you be willing
and obedient you going to eat the good
of the land and that's wherever you go
let alone the kingdom of heaven. Go
ahead and read this son. I mean
I miss you, brother.
Go ahead and read. Brother Strike. Go
ahead and read.
>> If thou shalt hearken unto the voice of
the Lord thy God to keep his
commandments and his statutes which are
written in this book of the law.
>> But that's how you get blessing access
to the tree of life and into the gates
in the city. Right.
>> Right.
>> Keep the commandments.
If you operate in the law and the
commandments that that is written in the
book of this law, go ahead and read.
>> And if thou turn into the Lord thy God
with all thine heart,
>> you got to come with all your heart.
Cuz like brother brother Stevie say that
old man in that that come up out of that
baptism pool chasing you, Jack.
>> I had to hang on to that. I'm like,
yeah, cuz I know that boy be on me. Like
I have to kick him down. Get on back,
man. You start grabbing the raid the
roast spray lights.
>> Get back.
>> You have to love the Lord and obey his
voice with all your heart. Turn to him
with all your heart. Cuz if you leave
any room open, Satan going to try to
enter into that void
>> on the real.
And what else, brother?
>> And with all thy soul.
>> And with all your body.
So you got to control your vessel as
well
cuz he whoever destroyed this
tabernacle, the Lord is going to be mad
at him.
So
we have to be obedient, sisters and
brothers.
These are instructions
to our obedience, for our obedience.
Verse 16, read.
>> And that I command thee this day to love
the Lord thy God,
>> to walk in his ways,
>> walk in his ways,
>> and to keep his commandments,
>> keep his commandments
>> and his statutes, and his judgments,
that thou mayest live and multiply.
>> That you can live and multiply.
Go ahead and read.
>> And the Lord thy God shall bless thee in
the land whether thou goest to possess
it.
>> Wherever you go, he going to bless you.
And sometimes he put that pressure on
you. put that fire on you like I like
that lesson you did brother uh Deshan
the affliction joint I don't know the uh
title in this totality I'm paraphrasing
but that was a good lesson we need that
pressure on us cuz we are being refined
and you can't be refin especially all
the dirt we got on us come here boiler
sir
>> remember them old uh them washing boards
back in the days
>> where you had to rub them co on that boy
to get it real clean the Lord trying to
scream all uh scratch all that scrub all
that filth off.
>> You know what I mean? So, it's going to
take some bumps and bruises sometime.
You going to have to go through some
things so you can obtain godliness.
All my life I've been learning,
you know, the things of the world, you
know what I mean? So, in order for me to
renew my mind and my heart to learn
godliness, I got to unlearn everything
that I learn. You see what I'm saying?
>> And therefore, the word of God is going
to purify us and clean us up. Like Jesus
said in John 3:15, "Now ye are clean by
the word that I have spoken unto you."
>> Did you finish that spanking?
>> Yes, I did.
However,
I want to keep reminding you about the
kingdom of God and about the power and
the glory for everlasting possession.
That's what we trying to get which God
has promised us if we obey his voice.
And I had to think about that. I'm like,
man, I'm longwinded. Hold on, Spanky.
He'd be looking at me like, yeah, come
on, man. Go to the next step. You ready
to read? Hold on. I was thinking about
it cuz you know it's a lot of things
that I want in this life. You know what
I mean? That the Lord say man is
entitled to. You know what I'm saying?
But he say seek
the righteousness of God in his kingdom
then everything else will be added.
Right.
>> Right. So, while I'm thinking on these
things that I want or that I desire, and
I ain't really focused on the kingdom of
God, why why do I want a new car when I
could have all power,
>> right?
>> Why do I want a lot of money when I
could be right next to Jesus and his
father? This is what he's giving us. But
in the meantime, before we get there, I
want to pour the house out steak.
No, keep your focus where it need to be,
people on God. Not not saying that, you
know what I'm saying? You can't delight
in in things of the world. And like the
Lord say, enjoy the fruits of your
labor.
But I'm coming to realize like don't
none of that matter to me no more
cuz hell is taking a long time for me to
get it. Okay, Lord, I get I'm just going
to focus on the kingdom. I got that bag
you want.
I'm I don't even want it no more. I'm
focus on your kingdom.
Let's finish. Let's go to uh Genesis 17
and 7 cuz this for everlasting
possession. And God will wear you out
like that. Like you you give up on it
like I don't even want it now. I'm
headed to the kingdom of God. You know
what I mean? You done suffer so long
without certain things. You like because
you trying to, you know, focus on God.
Keep your mind focused on him because he
put you to through these things so he
could break you like, "Oh, I can't I
ain't going to get it cuz I ain't doing
right by God." So you start to focus and
put your diligence in God. Now that
don't even mean nothing,
>> right?
>> He go that back. Oh, that ain't nothing.
I'm trying to when I'mma meet you. You
know what I mean?
Genesis 17-7. Go ahead and read. Let's
look at that everlasting possession that
he even told Abraham. This ain't nothing
new people. Go ahead and read.
>> And I will establish my covenant between
me and thee and thy seed after thee in
their generations. For
>> so who you talking to right here,
people. We talking to Abraham, right?
Read verse one so we can know who he's
talking about.
>> And when Abraham was 90 years old and
nine, the Lord appeared to Abraham and
said unto him,
>> what
>> I am all the almighty God.
>> Do what?
>> Walk before me and be thou perfect.
>> Walk before me and be thou perfect. Now
skip on down to verse seven and continue
to read to show you who he talking to.
>> And I will establish my covenant between
me and thee and thy seed after thee and
their generations. For
>> so if ye are Christ,
being baptized in Christ, then are you
Abraham's seed, no matter male or
female, Jew or Greek, free or bond, you
are Abraham's seed. So this covenant is
made with Abraham and us as well. Right?
Go ahead and read. And what is that?
>> In their generations for a everlasting
covenant.
>> For how long?
>> Everlasting.
>> Come on now, people. We got to do some
thinking. Go ahead and read.
>> To be a God under thee and to thy seed
after thee.
>> For how long?
>> For everlasting. Right. It's an
everlasting agreement. Right.
>> Right.
>> Do we live forever, people?
>> No, we don't.
>> So, what do we have to be to be
recipients of this type of covenant and
agreement?
What do WE HAVE TO HAVE? WHAT is our
life life expectancy supposed to be if
we going to take part in this covenant
and this agreement?
>> You got to live forever. Right.
>> Right.
>> There go the kingdom of heaven right
there. Cuz flesh and blood can't what?
Inherit the kingdom of God because it
don't live forever. Ever. Whether you in
the good side or the bad side. Even in
the lake of fire, you got to live
forever
>> cuz it's a everlasting punishment.
Now that's an agreement I don't want
forever. Right?
>> Verse eight, go ahead and read.
>> And I will give unto thee and to thy
seed after thee.
>> How long see the Lord coldblooded?
>> You talking about an inheritance. He
said, I'mma give unto thee and who else?
Spanky.
>> Thy seed and after thee.
>> And thy seed after thee. I'm going even
take care of your children.
Ain't that a blessing?
>> Yes, it is. So yo, who want to serve a
God that's only going to take care of
the parents and not the offspring?
I'm trying to serve this God that's
going to take care of me and my children
and my children's children, my
grandchildren
and their children and they children and
on and on and on. Y'all get the picture.
>> Read Spanky verse eight.
>> The land wherein thou art a stranger all
the land of Canaan. Pick it up at the
top again.
>> Okay. And all I will and and I will give
unto thee and to thy seed after thee.
>> What's that?
>> The land wherein thou art a stranger.
>> What is that?
>> All the land of Canaan.
>> All the land of Canaan. For how long?
>> For everlasting possession.
>> Come on now.
>> That mean you got to live there for 12
months.
>> Huh?
>> For 9 months?
>> No. Everlasting.
>> For how long you got to live in this
place if you going to possess it
forever? forever.
>> We talking about a transformation,
people.
>> Yeah.
>> And when I seen this one time when I
when I had just got out of that
baptismal pool in Minnesota, I was like,
he talking about the kingdom of God
right here to Abraham. And and and I was
oblivious to this. And I've read this
scripture time after time after time.
How can you be a recipient of this
covenant and you don't live forever?
That mean you got to be God
instead of a flesh and blood man.
And this how you know. Read my brother.
>> And I will be their God.
>> And he going to be our God.
Therefore take heed Revelation 21 and 7.
Revelation 21 and 7.
Revelation 21 and 7. A everlasting
possession.
That sound good to me?
>> Yes, it do.
>> The everlasting possession.
Take heed. And he said, I will be their
God. Revelation 21:7. Go ahead and read.
>> He that overcometh shall inherit all
things.
>> Some things.
>> All things.
>> A Volkswagen.
>> Over. He that inherit shall overcome
inherit all things.
>> A $2,000
coupon.
>> All things
>> for toy laws.
>> No, inherit all things.
>> You going to inherit all things. Go
ahead and read.
>> And I will be his God.
>> And he going to do what?
>> And he shall be my son.
>> And he going to be my son. Then he say,
I will give unto thee, and I see after
thee a land wherein thou art a stranger,
all the land of Canaan, for an
everlasting possession, and I will be
your God.
>> Yeah,
>> read it again, Spanky.
>> He that overcometh shall inherit all
things, and I will be his God, and he
shall be my son.
>> God is making good on what he said.
So you
can inherit the kingdom and the power
and the glory for how long?
>> Forever.
>> That's why it's a everlasting
possession.
Where new Jerusalem going to be at in
the land of Canaan, ain't it?
>> Mhm.
>> Kingdom of heaven. But
if you going to overcome and inherit all
things,
God got to instruct you, right?
>> Right.
on how you can reach that capacity.
Right? Y'all want to know the
instructions?
>> Yes, we do.
>> Do y'all
Let's see what the instruction is. The
Lord instruct his son. Proverbs 2 and 1.
Proverbs 2 and 1.
Cuz if you overcome yourself, if you
overcome this world, spoil the child.
You put a little rod on you. No, I'm
just joking.
I'm just joking. He all right. He all
right.
He that got an ear, let him hear what
the spirit say to the churches. He need
to hear all this. He going to be okay.
>> And this is what God instruct his son
cuz he say I will be his God and he will
be my son. Go ahead and read.
>> My son, if thou will receive my words,
>> you need what?
>> Receive my words.
>> What else? and hide my commandments with
thee. So that
>> you see the common denominator.
If you will receive the Lord's word and
hide his commandments with you, go ahead
and read
>> so that thou incline thine ear into
wisdom and apply thine heart to
understanding.
>> See, you got to apply this application
to your life, to your heart. That mean
it's got to be on your mind all the
time. When I wake up in the morning, I
pray to the Lord.
>> Yeah. and ask him when he when when I go
out, let the meditation of my heart and
the thoughts of my mind be stayed on
thee so I can have perfect peace
>> cuz if I don't I do something stupid,
>> right?
>> Go ahead and read.
>> Yeah. If thou criest after knowledge and
liftest up thy voice for understanding.
>> Y'all want understanding?
>> Yes, we do.
>> Lift up your voice for it. Talk to God.
I started crying to him cuz I'm like I
ain't look I don't know if you with me
no more like
man why you always crying like look I
need some result
but you can't force God's hand but the
book say cry out to him read it again
spanky
>> ye if thou cest after yay spanky he be
making up words
>> every time we be on the world road he be
making up stuff go ahead
>> yay if thou cry after the knowledge,
>> YOU GOT TO CRY OUT THE KNOWLEDGE. GO
AHEAD AND READ.
>> And liftest up thy voice for
understanding.
>> Mhm. Go ahead and read.
>> If thou seekest her as silver,
>> Yes, sir.
>> and searches for has for the third for a
I'm sorry. If thou seekest her as silver
and searchest for her as for a hidden
treasures.
>> Yes, sir. What you going to get?
>> Then shall then shalt thou understand
the fear of the Lord and what else?
>> And find the knowledge of God.
>> That's big right there, Jack.
You may find a 18 karat gold ring or a
diamond,
but when you find the knowledge of God,
that don't compare to it.
>> Yeah.
>> Which one of y'all have found the
knowledge of God? We all have. That's
why we here.
Before you had the knowledge of God, you
thought you was a a Baptist. What church
you go to?
First Missionary, Circle K, Walgreens
Baptist Church.
They got so many names and titles, but
ain't teaching nothing,
>> right?
>> So, we want to find the knowledge of
God, people. We want understanding and
the fear of the Lord. And you know what?
Once you find the knowledge of God,
guess who going to give it to you? Read
it.
>> For the Lord giveth wisdom.
>> Out of his mouth cometh knowledge and
understanding. So you getting your
knowledge and your wisdom and
understanding from the mouth of the
Lord.
Cuz then Jesus, we read in the beginning
that he came from heaven
>> not to speak his own words but to speak
the words of the father.
>> Mhm.
>> You ain't never had no present like
that. All the Christmas you kept when
you was shorty. And none of your gifts
amount to that.
Cuz I used to try to open mines early
before 12:00.
Man, ain't no Santa sell Santa Claus
coming. We in the projects. Ain't no ch.
Let us open them gifts.
But Jesus brought us this wisdom, this
knowledge and understanding straight
from the mouth of the father.
Psalms the first chapter.
So when you get this word, this wisdom
from the mouth of the Lord, this
knowledge and understanding, and you
learn to fear the Lord, you got to be
discreet.
>> Right. Right. Because you're not getting
in this kingdom willy-nilly. You're not
taking part of this kingdom and this
power and this glory forever just by
doing what you want to do. News flash.
Uh-uh.
Disclaimer.
Let's show you. You got to cut some
things off. Even some people
>> cuz in every house there's vessel
vessels of honor and vessels and
dishonor. Right? Look at my elder sister
agreeing with me like I know I'm in the
right place. So
cuz where did Jesus cast out the first
uh the devil
in the church? You said that son? Yeah.
Praise the Lord. You've been studying
huh? Yeah. Watching. Got my eye on you.
So he he said
I know who you is. You Jesus the son of
God.
Jesus was a Hebrew. HE SAID, "SHUT UP.
COME UP OUT of them."
>> And he came up out of them. So don't get
it twisted people.
They can be in here too.
>> Yeah.
>> Matter of fact, they are in here. Look,
he said they is. Look, he agree with me.
They is
>> on the real.
>> They is.
>> Grace and peace.
>> On the real. Happy Sabbath, beloved.
You better watch him though. You know
what I mean? And that's not to single
nobody out. That's not the point. No,
watch me. Hell
>> cuz you try to spit battle spit, right?
>> Brother Alvin done went awall, man. Get
him down ASAP. You talking about the
apocrypha now
>> because the Lord said the weed and the
tear, let them grow together, didn't he?
Yes, he did.
>> I'mma separate them at the harvest. So,
they in here, people
just want you to be mindful. But the
Lord gives us instruction. Go ahead and
read. Spank Psalm 101. Go ahead and
read.
>> Blessed the man that walketh not in the
counsel of the ungodly.
>> See, don't walk in the counsel of the
ungodly cuz you'll be blessed. GO AHEAD
AND READ.
>> Nor standeth in the way of sinners.
>> Don't stand in the way of sinners. Or do
what?
>> Nor siteth in the seat of the scorn.
>> Cuz there people like that.
got to remove yourself. What happened
with Dayton and Kora? All them people,
they got killed and the Lord swallowed
them up in the earth and had the earth
closed up on them. And then they told
Moses, "You killed the people of the
Lord." Lord, oh, you think you try?
>> Y'all didn't get enough from that.
And the Lord started killing up the
people where Aaron had to run with a
sensor and get between the living and
the dead to intercede for the people
because the Lord has sent the plague to
start killing up the congregation. So if
a little le like Stevie said in that
lesson, a little leaven leaven,
>> you better nip it in the bud while you
can.
>> And I got flaws people, sisters and
brothers. So I know this by experience.
It can grow up.
Weeds can grow up among the grass and
they look identical.
Oh, look like a servant of God, but when
that boy spring up, you'll know by the
conversation and the behavior that this
is a weed.
And you know what the weed and the tear
engagement is? The tear or the uh weed
do to the grass? It chokes it out.
So that mean
and I just got this from that brother is
he in my mind same spirit. Brother
Stevie said uh it'll affect the
congregation.
You know how you get a infection in your
body and you don't give it no attention
and it start to spread. Why you got them
bumps on your shoulder now?
It could end up becoming fatal affect
the whole body. Right. Go ahead and
read, Spanky.
>> But his delight is in the law of the
Lord.
>> Your delight got to be in the law of the
Lord. And and how much should you think
on the law of the Lord? Go ahead and
read.
>> And in his law do he meditate day and
night.
>> I got to get back to that.
Cuz once you step away from this book
and stop putting this book in you, you
could you would do anything. You'll
forget God like that.
>> Yes, he will.
>> I know. I'm living proof and I'm 52
years old and I got a lot of experience
on fighting with this mind and this
body.
And if you think you can uh overpower it
without the word of God, you going to
fall every time. I'm a preacher. I'm
here to tell you that. Mark my word.
Go ahead and read
>> verse four. The ungodly are not so, but
are like the the cha cha which the wind
driveth away. That's verse four. Spanky,
>> I thought you want me to read three. It
say
>> no. Go ahead and read. Read it again.
>> Okay. The ungodly are not so.
>> I thought you said verse six.
>> Oh, no. I said four.
>> The ungodly are not so. So, you want to
be godly, go ahead and read.
>> But are like the chafe which the wind
driveth away
>> like a potato chip bag and a heavy
windstorm. It just going to blow on off,
wipe you out. Go ahead and read.
>> Therefore, the ungodly shall not stand
in the judgment.
>> Right. nor sinners in the congregation
of the righteous.
>> So the ungodly, they ain't going to have
no foot to stand on when the Lord say go
to the fire.
Well, Lord, go to the fire
and they not going to stand in the
congregation of the righteous.
So in other words, continue in the
council of the Lord. And Jesus even
instructs us not to waste our time on
people that refuse to believe this word.
Matthew 7 and 6. Go ahead and read. Let
me get the people up out of here.
Matthew 7 and6.
Go ahead and read. That was a good
lesson, Brother Steve. You did. What was
it called? Uh
>> church hurt. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
And that just don't come from people
people uh
other people. It you can hurt your own
self if you're not applying this thing
to your life.
You know, sometimes you got to look at
you. You got to examine yourself. You
can't be pointing a finger.
Like brother Buie say, you pointing one
at somebody else and three pointing back
at you
>> cuz you put yourself in the position
of chaos as opposed to removing
yourself. Don't don't sit in the seat of
the scornful or stand in the counsel or
the ungodly. You gonna sit there and
listen to a person and then now he got
you all hot and bothered. Now you want
to reciprocate and hurt him because he
says something to you that was out of
pocket. You stayed there. You caused
that to happen to you. You caused your
own hurt.
>> Matthew 7:6. Let's show you what the
Lord say about people that don't want to
deal with this word. Go ahead and read.
>> Give not that which is holy un dogs.
>> Don't give that which is holy unto the
dogs. Go ahead and breathe.
>> Neither cast ye pearls before swine.
>> Man, Jesus was man. called him a dog.
Man, Jesus like that.
>> I thought you was the anointed one. You
done called that man a dog
>> and swine. Do not
give that which is holy to the dogs.
That's how God look at people that that
don't want to follow his truth.
You don't mean nothing. You a dog to
him.
And don't cast your pearls before swine.
Go ahead and read. This word is holy. Go
ahead and read.
>> Lest they trample them under their feet
and turn again and ren you.
>> Cuz they'll trample the word up under
their feet and turn again and start
dealing with you.
>> Yep.
>> Ren you mean they'll jump on you.
Like remember them seven sons ofKeva
and they went and tried to cast this uh
these these uh unclean spirits out of
this guy. And they said, "We we command
you to come out in the name of Jesus
that Paul preached." It said that spirit
jumped on them cats, beat them up out of
their clothes, RAN THEM OUT of the house
naked,
they'll deal with you,
especially if you phony kicking it.
But if you coming in the power of the
Lord, they gonna submit.
So you don't cast your pearls before
swine. You don't give that which is holy
to the dogs. Cuz if they don't care
about the word of God, what think what
what makes you think they going to care
about your life,
>> right?
>> That's why he said they going to turn
and ruin you. But this is what you do.
Titus 3 and 10. These just some basic
instruction that you need to take heed
to if you gonna take part of this
kingdom, this power, this glory forever.
Because this thing ain't for every
everybody.
And you got to know how to operate with
the sword of the spirit, with this
weapon that is not carnal that the Lord
has given us to get into this kingdom to
retrieve that power and obtain that
glory even forever.
Titus 3 and 10 because a lot of people
I get a lot of calls from brothers be on
Tik Tok and all that like and and out in
the world where I was telling the
brother and he said I'm like look bro he
don't believe in the word of God let
leave dude alone you know what I mean he
ain't trying to hear you bro matter of
fact look don't even call me no more
with that bro on the real cuz you
dealing with a dead corpse
What is a dead corpse going to do to you
>> and you communicating with it? It just
you study communicating with you look
crazy now. Why is he talking to a dead
body? He can't respond. They can't even
receive information.
Spiritual dead people can't even go
ahead and read verse 10. My brother
Titus 3 and 10 read. A man that is an
heretic after the first and second admon
admonition reject.
>> So after you give them two admonishment,
hey reject them or you'll end up causing
them to blasphe the word of God. They
already done showed you that they don't
believe and they don't want to hear and
you study keep trying to talk to them,
trying to drive it home to them. Now you
causing them to blasphe the word of God
because you won't let them go and leave
them alone. reject them
after two admonishment.
Jeremiah 33 and3
the Lord got a message by the mouth of
Jeremiah.
Let's show you what the Lord say to us
all people.
Go ahead and read. Thank you.
>> Call unto me and I will answer thee and
I will show thee great and mighty things
which thou knowest not.
>> See, the Lord has given us instructions
on how to live in this life, even in the
world tomorrow.
That's why I read this book. That's why
I trust in the Lord. That's why I call
on him and make prayer and supplication
unto my God. Not only for me, for my
children, for my fellow brothers and
sisters in Christ,
for the peoples that's incarcerated, for
the fatherless, the widows, the sick and
the shut in, the homeless and the
hungry, the poor, the meek of the earth,
those that's standing on the uh streets
with signs, asking for money.
You have to consider the Lord's creation
and what they are going through in their
adversity and maybe he'll consider you
cuz this way of life even godliness is
not what people made it up to be.
It's bigger than keeping the Sabbath.
It's bigger than not just eating pork.
is bigger than just knowing the 10 or
the 70 weeks of Daniel or who the
abomination of desolation is. It's
bigger than that. It's about changing
your mind and your ways and your
perspective of life so you can submit
yourself to God. So he could exalt you
in due time.
And a lot of people don't see that.
Call on me and I'mma answer you and
I'mma show you great and mighty things
which thou knowest not. I thought it was
just about the Sabbath day. No, it's
about me recovering the whole creation.
God is telling us all,
"Come to me
for all our needs."
And he going to show us things to come.
And he going to show you how to bring it
to pass.
For his is the kingdom, his is the
power, his is the glory forever.
>> Amen.
>> He know how to He know how to deal with
whatever is in this creation.
He know how to make it last.
Go to verse eight, spanky, and read.
>> And I will cleanse them from all their
iniquity, whereby they have sinned
against me, and I will pardon all their
iniquities whereby they have sinned.
>> Where you at?
>> You said verse 8. Jeremiah 33. and Nate.
>> Oh, you Oh, let's go to uh Matthews. My
fault.
>> Mhm.
>> My fault, Spanky. That was my bad. I I
went through a tangent, bro.
>> It's all good. You said that.
>> Let's go to Matthew the 7th chapter.
>> Okay.
>> Cuz God shows us how to utilize this
capacity of this earth and subdue it so
we could take part in the world of Mar
and know how to have dominion over that
world. Go ahead and read verse seven.
Ask and it shall be given you.
>> Seek and you shall find.
>> Knock.
>> Knock and it shall be open unto you.
>> See, God is telling you how he can show
you all things and give you
understanding on mighty things and great
things and show you how they operate so
you can know how to deal in that
kingdom. Verse eight, Spank, go ahead
and read.
>> For everyone that asks, receive it.
>> Everyone that asks, do what? Spanky?
>> Receive it.
>> But you got to do right by God. You'll
get it. Go ahead and read. And he that
seeketh findeth.
>> And if you seeking it, the Lord allow
you to find it. Go ahead and breathe.
>> And to him that knockketh, it shall be
open.
>> And if you knocking, the Lord going to
open it up for you. Let's go to Matthew
the 6th chapter, brother.
>> Fifth or the sixth?
>> Did you read verse eight?
>> Yeah, that was the end of eight. We
should be on Matthew 5 and 42.
>> Let's go to Matthew the 6th chapter.
>> Okay. He said, "For everyone that
askketh receiveth, and he that seeketh
findeth, and to him that knockketh it
shall be open." Request is granted,
people. However, there's a way that
Jesus tell us how to petition the
father.
>> Make your calling and election sure.
Make it known unto your father what you
need,
according to his to his uh commandments,
though, not according to your own lust
of what you desire, but according to his
will, and he'll grant it to you.
>> Mhm.
>> Matthew 6 and6. And let's see how we ask
the father or petition the father.
Father, go ahead and read. But thou,
when thou prayest, enter into the
closet, and when thou hast shut thy
door, pray to thy father which is in
secret.
>> So you got to give God his time. Get
along with him and converse with him.
Don't be all in front of Walmart. Lord,
you know the hypocrites get stand on
stand at the head of the street praying
like when we went out uh to give the uh
give out sandwiches and stuff and potato
chips to uh to the people down at C and
you know give them something to drink,
give them something to to eat on and
give them the word of God. There was
another church down there. They came and
sat under our tent, you know what I
mean? And they was listening. And then
they one jumped up and said out of the
other church, he was like, "Uh, let us
all pray." You ain't praying.
I'm praying. I don't know that God you
dealing with. I know what God I'm
dealing with. I ain't going to let you
pray over me.
>> I'm f to pray cuz I know what a God I'm
dealing with. I don't know what God you
dealing with. So you have to know what
God you praying to. But pray to him in
secret. Go in your closet and shut your
door. And the father which seeth in
secret going to reward reward you
openly. Go ahead and read. Spank. Did
you finish that?
>> I'm about to finish it now.
>> Go ahead.
>> And thy father which seeth in secret
shall reward thee openly.
>> Mhm. Once again. The Lord's instruct you
to come and buy of me gold tried in the
fire. And when you are asking anything
of the father, this how you come to him.
Verse nine.
>> After this manner, therefore pray ye our
father which are in heaven.
>> Acknowledge. I know you my father and I
know where you dwell at in heaven. Go
ahead and read.
>> Hallowed be thy name.
>> And holy is your name, father.
The same name that Jesus came in. Right.
Right.
>> That's Jesus the anointed one in
English. the Christ.
But don't take my word for it. Jesus can
speak for himself.
Let's read Zechariah 2 and 8.
Zechariah 2 and 8.
Zechariah 2 and 8. Should I get an hour
and a half?
>> I ain't never did an hour and a half.
>> Try to pull it off. Read, my brother.
>> For thus sayeth the Lord of hosts.
>> Mhm.
>> After the glory hath he sent me unto the
nations which spoiled you.
>> Hold on. Who can send the Lord of hosts?
>> Angels.
>> The Father. Go ahead and read.
For he that touches you touchth the the
apple of his eye.
>> The one that sent Jesus holy or hollow
be his name. In his own name he sent
Jesus to redeem us people because when
they touch you, they touch the apple of
the father's eye. Did you know that
>> all the time you was in channel slavery?
You know they was touching the father
the apple of the father's eye.
when they pull you over and and and
wrongfully accuse you or shoot people
down that you know what I'm saying they
have no no probable cause to do so just
because out of racism or whatever vice
versa black man against uh a gentile or
European when you act races racist
towards them you you you you uh you
touching the apple where the fathers are
especially if they in the covenant with
God
>> and in most cases even if they ain't
because God is not a respector of
person. He said he that fearth him and
and and do well is accepted with him.
You know there's no discrimination with
God. We all are brothers and sisters
out of no matter what nationality
because Noah had three sons. Ham, Sam,
and J Fat. And we all come up out of one
of them sons.
So he sent Jesus
to redeem us and he resent. When he sent
Jesus, he sent redemption into the
earth. Psalm 111
and N9.
when he sent Jesus to save mankind, even
to salvage us and recover us from the
sin that we failed
from the glory that he positioned us in
the beginning. He sent him to recover us
and to make an atonement for us,
>> right? to be the propitiation for our
sins, to pay for our debt
that we are charged with for offending
God.
Go ahead and read, my brother. Jesus is
our redemption program. Go ahead and
read.
>> He sent redemption unto his people. He
had commanded his covenant forever.
>> What's his name?
>> Holy and reverend is his name.
>> That's right. Our Father, which art in
heaven, hallowed be thy name. Thy
kingdom come, thy will be done in earth
as it is in heaven. Give us this day our
daily bread. And forgive us not our
debts as we forgive our debts. Forgive
those because the Lord forgive you
people, those that are fearing you
and to fear him and to obey the true and
living God. We would be wise to do so.
Read verse 10, my brother.
>> The fear of the Lord is the beginning of
wisdom. A good understanding have all
they that do his commandments. His
praise endureth forever.
>> See, fear of the Lord is the beginning
of wisdom. And you have a good
understanding if you keep his
commandment. But if you don't keep his
commandment, I ask you where the book of
Genesis at and you don't know where it
is. That tell me how much understanding
you got.
Well, I ask you uh when is the Lord's
Sabbath day and you say the first day of
the week or floating Sabbath. That tells
me how much understanding you got.
>> And if you keep the commandments or not,
>> you need to know who you dealing with
people.
However, he that saith I know and
keepeth not his commandment is a lie and
the truth is not in him. I ain't make
that up. The Bible say that. But blessed
are they that do his commandments that
they may have right to the tree of life
and enter in through the gates and to
the city or you not getting this power
nor this kingdom nor this glory
forever.
Matthew 6:10.
Keep these commandments that you may
have right to the tree of life and may
enter in through the gates into the
city. When my brother, when is that
going to take place? Read.
>> Thy kingdom come. Thy will be done in
earth as it is in heaven.
>> When his kingdom come, when his will be
done in earth as it is in heaven, when?
Revelation 21 and 3,
when my brethren,
when is this kingdom coming?
And when will his will be done in earth
as it is in heaven? Revelation 21 and3
read.
>> And I heard a great voice out of heaven
saying behold the tabernacle of God is
with men and he will dwell with them and
they shall be his people and God himself
shall be with them and be their God.
>> And that's when it's going to take
place. All those that kept his
commandments and follows his
instructions. Right? Because that's what
he told Abraham. I will make a covenant
with thee and thy seed after thee to
give you the land of Canaan for
everlasting possession and I will be
your God.
This is the conclusion of the matter.
Isaiah 46 and10.
All of us that keep his commandment and
follow his instructions, we going to
take part in this kingdom, this power
with this glory even forever. Right?
And this same thing he told Abraham, why
is we reading the same thing in the last
B in in the last book of the Bible that
we read in the first book of the Bible?
Read. Thank you.
>> Declaring the end from the beginning
>> because he declared the end from the
beginning. name Genesis the beginning.
>> Mhm.
>> Then he tell Abraham he was going to
inherit the land of uh Canaan for
everlasting possession and I will be
your God.
>> Mhm.
>> Why is he telling Abraham something that
we can read in Revelation? Because he
declared an end from the beginning. Go
ahead and read.
>> And from ancient times to things that
are not yet done say my counsel shall
stand
>> and what?
>> And I will do all my pleasure
>> in earth as it is in heaven.
And this is the same directive that God
gave us even from the beginning of man.
Ephesians 5 and1.
Can I make 130 hour and 30 minutes? Oh
no. This is unusual.
Frankie, you cool?
>> I'm good, man.
Something wrong, bro.
>> Ephesians 5 and one. Go ahead and read
what we got to do.
>> By ye therefore followers of
>> Hold on. Hold on. Spanky. Come on, man.
You're a professional reader, man.
Stepping on toes, man.
>> I won't do it. I got you.
>> Come on, man.
Get your game right or you out of here.
>> Go ahead and read, bro. By ye therefore
follow
>> I'm sorry about yay. Sorry that
>> Oh yeah, you right. I saw that. My
fault. My fault. My fault.
>> I don't know. He must You feeling good,
Spank? You good? It's okay.
>> I got you.
>> Oh, man.
>> One more time, Spank.
>> All right, here we go. Be ye therefore
followers of God and dear children.
>> Be ye followers of God as dear children.
Let's follow God, people. He can't
direct you
to somewhere he don't want you to go or
somewhere you don't want to be. He ain't
going to give you wrong directions.
And when you follow God, what else you
able to do? Spanky in verse 10.
>> Proving what is acceptable unto the
Lord.
>> You know what the Lord accept? And you
know what the Lord rejects? Let's go to
Isaiah 55 and3.
Follow God. Prove what is acceptable
unto the Lord.
And this is how you do that. Isaiah 55
and3.
They ain't going to let me make an hour
and 30 cuz they taking all day. Go ahead
and read.
>> Incline your ear.
>> Listen. Go ahead and read.
>> And come into me.
>> Come unto the Lord. Go ahead and read.
>> Hear and your soul shall live
>> even forever. Right. Thank you.
>> Forever.
>> Let's validate it. Read.
>> And I will make an everlasting covenant
with you.
>> How you going to make an everlasting
covenant with somebody that don't live
forever?
>> Who is that? Go ahead and read.
>> Even the sure mercies of David.
>> That is Jesus. The sure mercy of David.
Skip on up to verse one. Let him
instruct you on how to take part in this
kingdom, this power, this glory forever.
Read.
>> Oh, everyone that thirst thirsteth.
>> Are you thirsty?
Come get you some Kool-Aid. Go ahead and
read.
>> Come ye to the waters and he
>> the living waters.
>> The living waters.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> And he that have no money, come ye buy
and eat. Yeah. Come buy wine and milk
without money and without price.
>> You ain't even got to pay for it.
So don't let nobody tell you lock the
door till we get 40,000.
You ain't got to pay for this.
come back wine and milk without money
and without price. Go ahead and read.
>> Wherefore do you spend money for that
which is not bread?
>> Why you paying money for for nothing
ain't going to get you salvation
or something that can't get you eternal
life? Go ahead and read.
>> And your labor for that which satisf.
>> Why you working for the pastor pageant
or the first lady of the church, right?
>> And they can't get you salvation
cuz you cooked them fried chicken. That
ain't don't give you no brownie points
with the Lord.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> Hearken diligently unto me.
>> You got to listen to the Lord.
Watching the washing all the the the the
the cars in the church don't get you
nowhere with the Lord.
>> Having a church car wash, that don't get
you nowhere to with the Lord.
>> Church car wash.
>> Having a church function that keep God's
commandments get you somewhere with the
Lord. That's the currency that he want
to see.
Go ahead and read.
>> And eat ye that which is good, and let
your soul delight in itself in fatness.
And
>> eat this word of God. Eat my flesh and
drink my blood,
and it will evolve into everlasting
life. Then you going to delight yourself
in fatness,
even everlasting life. Revelation 3 and
20. Read
Revelation 3 and 20. Cuz
Jesus will even do dash on you if you
want to eat something this good
spiritual food.
>> He said door dash on.
>> Ain't that's when they show up at your
house with the food.
>> Yes, they do. That's That's it.
>> I show you who was door dashing first.
>> Revelation 3 and 20. What did he say?
>> Behold, I stand at the door and knock.
>> Dingdong.
Who there? Go ahead and read.
>> If any man hear my voice and open the
door, I will come in to him.
>> And what he going to do?
>> And I will suck with him and he with me.
>> And he going to even eat some of that
door dash with you.
>> I will come in and suck with him and he
with me. I'm going to eat the same word
that I give you. I'm not a hypocrite.
I'm giving you something that's going to
lead you to all power and everlasting
life. How you think I got there?
Romans the 8th chapter tell you that
is the spirit of him that raised Jesus
from the dead or Christ from the dead
dwell in you.
>> That same spirit shall also quicken your
mortal bod
that same spirit
that raised up Jesus from the dead which
dwelleth in you
because he's going to deal with the same
thing that he has given us.
Therefore, we should be praying
for this always, people,
for this is spiritual consumption.
Matthew 6 and 11.
But Jesus come in and feed you and what
he himself has eaten as well.
We we want to consume this every day.
Every day.
Are you thinking the Lord's prayers and
say this? Go ahead and read respect.
>> Give us this day our daily bread.
>> Every day. Luke 11:3.
Give us this day our daily bread.
Cuz he that eat of that bread shall
never die.
>> Right.
>> And we gonna validate that. Give us this
day our daily bread.
Luke 11 and3. How long my brother read?
>> Give us day by day our daily bread.
>> Give us day by day this daily bread. You
better eat some of this every day.
I try to keep this this this word on my
mind all the time. I don't listen to
music. I don't watch TV, anything that's
in the secular world until I deal with
the word of God in my day in in the
beginning of my day. I ain't saying you
ain't you got to do that, but that's
what I do.
You see what I'm saying? If I deal with
anything in the world of the world,
I'mma deal with what I need to deal with
with God first.
Cuz if I put him first, maybe he'll put
me on his list.
John 6 and 50.
This bread come from heaven as we seen
in the beginning. This had to come from
the father.
>> Read Spanky.
>> This is the bread which cometh down from
heaven.
>> Yes sir.
>> That a man may eat thereof and not die
>> through Jesus Christ the high priest.
The word and the lamb. Even the
sacrifice of God. By his stripes we are
healed.
He brought that word. This word came
from heaven. This is the bread that you
need daily. Cuz if you eat of this bread
and believe it, Spanky, how long you
going to live?
>> Forever.
>> Would you die?
>> Nope.
>> You'll never die. Me and Spanky, we
believe that, don't we?
>> Yes, we do.
>> And all my brothers and sisters in here
believe that. Psalms,
>> we'll make it.
>> Read verse 451. My brother,
>> I am the living bread which came down
from heaven. Praise the Lord. Go ahead
and read.
>> If any man eat of this bread,
>> Yes, sir.
>> he shall live forever.
>> How did Eve and them get deceived in the
garden? They ate of the tree of the
knowledge of good and evil. Right.
Right.
>> So that mean they listen to Satan, the
devil, which was the serpent, or that
tree of the knowledge of good and evil.
So if you eating of the bread that Jesus
is telling you to eat of, which is him,
then you eating what he is giving you,
the word of God.
The word of God. Go ahead and read
Spank.
>> And the bread that I will give is my
flesh.
>> For what?
>> Which I will give for the life of the
world.
>> Because he's going to die for the sins
of the world as well as bringing you the
message to get you back in good grace
with the father as him being the
sacrifice even the high priest to make
intercession for the world and take away
the sins of the world. Psalm 69-6.
So he gonna intercede on our behalf.
People, let's put him on the witness
stand so he can
show you how he interceded on our
behalf. Y'all want to see how Jesus
interceded on our behalf?
>> Yeah.
>> Y'all want to hear hear uh firsthand
Psalm 69. What did Jesus say to the
father for our sake, brother? Go ahead
and read.
>> Let not them that wait on thee. LET NOT
US THAT WAIT on the father guard and
read.
>> Oh Lord God of hosts.
>> Oh Lord the God of host guard and read.
>> be ashamed for my sake.
>> Don't let us be ashamed for Jesus sake.
Don't let them be ashamed father for my
sake. Why is that my brother?
>> Let not those that seek thee be
confounded for my sake.
>> Don't let them that seek you, father be
confused for my sake.
>> Keep reading my brother. Oh God of
Israel.
>> Yes sir. Read.
>> Because of thy for because for thy sake
I have borne reproach.
>> Because for you father I bear reproach.
Go ahead and read.
>> Shame have covered my face.
>> And shame have covered my face. They
spit in my face. They snatched my beard
out. They put a crown of thorns on my
hand. They nailed my hands and my feet
>> so I can recover them that's doing it.
Finish that up. Flanky.
>> Oh, that is
>> Read it again.
>> Because of Because for thy sake I have
borne reproach.
>> Mhm.
>> Shame hath covered my face.
>> Wait. Go ahead.
>> I am be I am become a stranger to my
brethren and an alien to my mother's
children.
>> Just because
he going to die for us. He going to take
the fall for us, the punishment for us.
He said he came to his own and his own
received him not. We are his own people.
>> Yes, we are.
>> And if we didn't find out of this word,
find out this word, we wouldn't receive.
>> Let's go to John 16 and 23.
Because Jesus paid the price for our
sins, therefore is
salvation
able to be obtained.
He is our only access to the father.
So all our prayers must be to the father
in Jesus' name.
>> All our prayers.
Prove us. Thank you. And in that and in
that day ye shall ask me nothing.
>> Don't ask me nothing. This who you ask.
Go ahead and read.
>> Verily, verily, I say unto you,
whatsoever ye shall ask the father in my
name, he
>> whatsoever you ask f the father or God
in my name, what's going to happen?
>> He will give it to you.
>> He going to give it to you cuz he paid
the price for us.
>> In Jesus' name, the way, the truth, and
the life.
And no man can come unto the father but
by him. Romans 3 and 25.
Romans 3 and 25.
We got one more scripture after this and
we done people.
Romans 3 and 25.
Jesus is the truth,
the way, and the life. And no man come
to the father but by him. He is the one
that came down from heaven to give us
the word of the father which is in
heaven which no man have never seen his
shape or either heard his voice at any
time. So how you going to get the
information from an invisible God that
you can't even approach? You have to
have an inner mediator and that is Jesus
the Christ
who died for the sins of the entire
world. Read it my brother.
>> Whom God has sent forth to be a propit
propitiation
through faith in his blood.
>> For God sent him to be an atonement to
atone for our sins to pay the ransom and
to give his life a ransom for many that
we should be saved. Go ahead and read.
>> To declare his righteousness for the
remission of sins.
>> To declare God's righteousness on how we
need to walk even for the remission of
sin. The forgiveness of our past sin. Go
ahead and read. that our past
>> go and read
>> through the forbearance of God
>> because God has suffered along with us
and he is not slack concerning his
promise of what he gonna do to this
earth and the wicked or to the righteous
but he is longsuffering towards us with
willing that none should perish but that
all should come to repentance
cuz do he any have any pleasures in the
wicked that he should die
>> and not that he should turn from his
ways and live Right?
>> That's the only reason why we ain't
being consumed. Cuz God got patience and
longsuffering.
>> So if he could suffer along with me to
get my life right, maybe I could wait a
little bit longer for him to answer my
prayer.
>> I ain't got no choice anyway.
You the recipient,
right?
So the blood is Jesus Christ
through that blood
that the father will forgive us
for our sins.
And what else? Thank you. Matthew 6:12
by Jesus blood.
He is the propitiation
or the ransom of the world
or the restitution
that God received and is appeased with
so we can be saved and get back to
godhood
or reach godhood and the potential or
not dying when he created man. Man were
created to die. Death was not a part of
this creation.
I said, "Ye are gods, and all of ye are
the children of the most high, but ye
shall die like men and fall like one of
the princes."
We fail greatly.
So he sent his son Jesus
to shed his blood so he would forgive us
for our sins. And what else? Thank you.
and forgive us of our debts
>> as we forgive our debtors.
>> And what else?
>> And lead us not into temptation.
>> And lead us not into temptation. What
else?
>> But deliver us from evil.
>> And deliver us from evil. Why?
>> For thine is the kingdom and the power
and the glory forever
>> in Jesus mighty name. Amen. Thank you
for your time. I hope somebody got some
understanding. In the mighty name of
Jesus Christ.
dream.
Hey
Word Jesus,
Lord.
>> Will you wash me?
>> Will you please
me? Lord, make me home.
>> Will you wash me?
>> Wer than snow.
>> Sometimes, Lord, this life is rough.
>> At times we feel we've had enough.
But with all the sin in the world today,
we need you Lord to wash us clean.